Guide to the Roy Lisker Papers, 1957 -
Roy Lisker Papers 1957 -
- Old box 48
  (11) “MMT 8”: The Music Lesson, 4th and 5th revisions
  (12) Editorial of April 13
  (13) Irreversible motion in Space, a thought experiment April 13, 2009
  (14) Travel Notebooks and Journals: August-November 2008
  (15) MMT 5, 6, 7: Revision Pages
- Old box 49
  boxes 80-82
  (1) Hysteria and Enlightenment, Chapters 1 and 2 (Mesmer / Marie-Therese von Paradis) Revised Version of December 2008
  (2) MMT 1 Revisions
  (3) MMT 3 Revisions
  (4) MMT 4 Revisions
  (5) Texts for talks given at the University of Illinois in Chicago, February 2009, with revisions
  (6) Sketches for a detective story, Cambridge Mass, 1964
  (7) Notebook, San Diego July 18,2002
  (8) Poetry Experimental Notebook, October 2008
  (9) “El Pessebre” Pages 1-36, first revision November 2008 To Be Continued January 21
  (10) El Pessebre Chapters 1 and 2 (Original typescript of 1979)
  (11) Journal, June 2008 to January 2009 Indexed
  (12) MMT 5 - proof-reading revisions
  (13) March 2008 Mathematics Research Journal Indexed
  (14) May 2008 Mathematics Research Journal Indexed
  (15) Math and Science Journal PENROSE REVIEW July 2005 Indexed
  (16) June 2005 Math Research Journal "Math Manual Problem Sets"
  (17) Tindy Agaba's Thesis
  (18) El Pessebre Revision pages May 09 Chapters 2-8
- Old box 50
  boxes 82-83
  (1) Notes for a paper "General Relativity and Collisions" hand-written
  (2) Grand Plan, August 2002. Review with marginalia December 2009
  (3) El Pessebre; original text of 1979 pages 43-73
  (4) El Pessebre, first revision December 29th, 2009: City Hall episode
  (5) Perpignan, August 2009: travel notes Typescript
  (6) Perpignan, text for upload on Ferment Magazine December 22
  (7) Sketches Notebook, October 3rd, 2008. Taken on European trip Aug-Oct 2009
  (8) Editorial, June 10, 2009
  (9) Mesmer/Marie-Therese Finale, Chapter 12 (July 10, 2009)
  (10) Journal, June 08- Jan 09: Notes for a "kaleidoscopic novel" of periods lived in Cambridge, Mass.
  (11) Mesmer-Marie Therese, Notes
  (12) El Pessebre: From "Oratorio" to "Baker/Montoya"
  (13) Perpignan Travelogue, 1st revision
  (14) Poems, transcribed and sent to Emma Thompson, every Thursday for one year (April 26, 2006)
  (15) El Pessebre, Transcription Part II: Pages 1-90
  (16) Travelogue, England 2009 Revisions December 5, 2009
  (17) Notebook, July 20, 2009 (not indexed)
  (18) June 2008: Cambridge/Boston notebook
  (19) Travelogue, Europe 2009: First revision
  (20) Ireland Travelogue - 2nd revision
  (21) Budget Journal January 2007 to January 2008
  (22) Road Journal, June/August 2007 (written in both directions)
  (23) MMT 11 - First revision June 2009
  (24) Editorials, June 17th, 2009
  (25) El Pessebre Chapter 12 May 16, 2009
  (26) Essay for 75th anniversary party of John Basinger
  (27) El Pessebre, Chapters 6-11, First revision
  (28) El Pessebre Chapters 1-5 Second revision
  (29) MMT 10 "The Fantastic Garden" Revisions of May 19, 2009
  (30) Editorial May 22, 09: Israel/Palestine
  (31) El Pessebre 1st revision Chapter 1
  (32) John Basinger tribute, editing
- Old box 51
  boxes 83-84
- Old box 52
  boxes 84-85
- Old box 53
  boxes 85-86
- Old box 54
  boxes 86-87
- Old box 55
  boxes 87-89
- Old box 56
  boxes 89-90
- Old box 57
  boxes 90-91
- Old box 58
  boxes 91-92
- Old box 59
  boxes 92-94
- Old box 60
  boxes 94-95
- Old box 61
  boxes 95-96
- Old box 62
  boxes 96-97
- Old box 63
  boxes 98-99
- Old box 64
  boxes 99-100